

LAZARO NASCIMENTO
FULL STACK WEB3 DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Full Stack Web3 Developer with 6+ years of experience building web and blockchain solutions. I always strive to achieve the perfect result. It is nothing that is not perfect. I am a fast-learner, self-starter and good team player. Looking for opportunities to make a long-term contribution as a full stack web3 developer.

CONTACT nascimento.dev26@gmail.com

(84) 99615-9014

Avenida Açude Santa Rita de Cássia, 19

Natal, RN, Brazil 59010

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Bodybuilding • Football • Art • Theatre • Environmental Conversation • Travel

EXPERIENCE

BLOCKCHAIN FULLSTACK DEVELOPER, PHURSHELL, SAO PAULO, BRAZIL

MARCH 2021-MAY 2022

As a full stack developer, participated in developing apps like BuyApp, Goplayer and Goplayer Gestor. Responsible for rewriting backend logic and DB-related work for storing and indexing blockchain transaction data. Refactored solidity code on deployed NFTs and redeployed. Code review on React Native frontend code, quality assurance and performance optimization.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER, NEXTLY, SAO PAULO, BRAZIL

AUGUST 2017-JANUARY 2021

After turned over to a full stack developer, participated in building a lot of web solutions for many big companies and startups from all around the world. Worked on backend with Python, Node.js, Golang, PHP and Java. Worked on frontend with React and React Native. Worked with various databases like Dgraph, Neo4j, MongoDB, Postgres and MySQL. Integrated third party services and platforms like Stripe, Google APIs, AWS services and so on. Played a key role in problem solving and troubleshooting.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, NEXTLY, SAO PAULO, BRAZIL

FEBRUARY 2016-AUGUST 2017

Implemented UI/UX design in to React components and integrated them with backend APIs. Played an outstanding role in data visualization projects and demonstrated my coding skills and deep knowledge of data structure and algorithms

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN INFORMATION SECURITY

UFMG, MG, BRAZIL JANUARY 2016 DEAN'S LIST/2015

KEY SKILLS

Solidity • Python • Node.js • Golang • Java • React • React Native Next.js • Gatsby • NestJS • Strapi • Firebase • CI/CD pipelines • NFT • DeFi • Stripe • Docker • Graph Database • MongoDB • SQL • DevOps • Deep Learning • WebRTC • AWS